So, thanks for coming by, guys.
We just wanted to bounce
some ideas off of you
about the wedding ceremony.
Oh...
What's the matter?
Are you okay?
Yeah, it's just, you know...
Monica said, "Wedding."
MONICA:
Uh, so, we wanted to
know if one of you
would like to read something
at the ceremony.
Okay, yeah
I guess...
I guess I could do that, too.
"Too"?
Yeah, I kind of, uh
( clearing throat ):
have something else planned
for you guys.
Oh. Do you mind telling us
what it is?
Sorry, I'm kind of keeping
this one on the QT.
Well, whatever it is,
I hope it involves winking.
Hey!
OTHERS:
Hey.
I just talked
to one of the DOOL writers...
What is DOOL?
Days of our Lives.
Oh.
Anyway, you're not going
to believe it--
my character is coming
out of his coma!
Hey, that's great!
That's great!
Joey!
And-And-And
not only that
I'm getting a new brain!
So, great things are
happening at work
and in your
personal life.
RACHEL:
Wait.
What do you mean
you're getting a new brain?
Well-Well,
they're killing off
one of the characters
on the show
and when she dies,
her brain is being transplanted
into my body.
Wh-What?
A brain transplant?
It's ridiculous!
Well, I think
it's ridiculous
that you haven't had sex
in three and a half months.
It's winter.
There are fewer people
on the street.
Who are they killing off?
Uh, Cecilia Monroe.
She plays
Jessica Lockhart.
No...
She is so good
at throwing drinks
in people's faces.
I mean, I don't think
I've ever seen her finish
a beverage.
MONICA:
And the way
she slaps people
all the time.
Wouldn't you love
to do that just once?
Don't do it.
And she's been
on the show forever.
It's going to be really hard
to fill her shoes.
Yeah, yeah.
Help me out here.
When you... when
you come out of the
"brain transplant"
you are going
to be her?
Yes, but in
Drake Ramoray's body.
( mumbles incredulously )
Why is it so hard
for you to get?
I thought you were
a scientist.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Rach, so,
that guy there...
straight or gay?
RACHEL:
Oh...
( laughing ):
Oh, yeah, he's too
cute to be straight.
Ooh, Knockers will help us
figure it out.
Oh.
All right,
straight...
and not subtle.
Ooh, he left
his cell phone.
Oh.
Well, we can give
it to Gunther
and he'll put it
in lost and found.
Or we could use it
to call China
see how those guys
are doing.
What if, um, if he calls
his own cell phone
to find out who found it
and I answer and
we start talking
and we fell in love?
I mean, wouldn't that
be a great story?
Kind of like a fairy tale
for the digital age.
Yeah...
that does sound great.
I'm going
to get the phone.
What? Wait!
Wh-Why... why do
you get the story?
I don't know.
I haven't been
out on a date in so long.
Phoebe, you had a
date three days ago.
That wasn't a date.
That was...
that was just friends
getting together...
having sex.
Okay. Great.
See? I get the phone.
No way.
You just broke up with Tag
a week ago.
Yeah, and until now...
( voice breaking ):
I didn't think
I would love again.
Nice try.
Well, hey, wait, wait.
How do we fairly decide
who gets the phone?
I don't know.
Well, um...
maybe we
could... uh...
Aha, too slow!
( laughing cockily )
Aha!
Too cocky.
I'm going to keep
dating him, Mother
and there's nothing
you can do about it.
Oh, yes, there is.
What are you going to do,
kill him
like you did Charles?
Oh, my baby!
( sobs once )
MAN:
Cut.
( scattered applause )
That was a great scene.
An-And that slap
looked so real.
How do you do that?
Oh, just years
of experience.
( crying ):
Can I get
some ice here?
Well, anyway,
I just wanted
to say how wonderful
I think you are.
You're not the fan
who's dying, are you?
Uh, no.
No, I'm Joey
Tribbiani.
We did a scene
together yesterday.
I'm the guy
in the coma.
Oh, that was
a real person?
( stammers softly )
A-A-Anyway, I just
wanted to say
that since I'm getting
your brain when
you leave the show
I was wondering if
there's any tips...
Wait. I-I'm leaving the show?
I don't know. Why?
Did you hear something.
Who told you that?
Uh... uh...
one of the writers.
Which writer?
Was it bald
or was it tall?
Uh, you know, uh...
You know what?
It doesn't matter,
because it is not true.
Okay.
And if it were true,
how dare you come to me
and ask me for tips
about a character
that I've been playing
for 20 years.
I'll give you a tip.
Miss Monroe...
Oh, there you go.
Okay, look,
I have an idea.
Why don't we...
why don't we see
what kind of numbers he
has on his speed dial?
And, then, from that,
we can tell who has
more in common with him
and, then, whoever
does, gets the phone.
Fine. All right.
All right.
First name on the
speed dial is "Mom."
Oh...
I lost my mom
to suicide.
Okay, no way.
You cannot use that
to get the cute guy
and the last
blueberry muffin.
Did I use that
already today?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
"Ben... Carlos...
David..."
Oh, I win.
He's got Barney's
on his speed dial.
So, you don't know
that it's Barney's, the store.
That could be, you know,
his friend's house or a bar.
Who has Barney's, the store,
on their speed dial?
His new girlfriend.
( bagpipes droning dissonantly)
What is that?
I think it's the
Dying Cat Parade.
It sounds like it's coming
from across the street.
Oh, my God.
What?
You know that thing
that Ross was going
to do at our wedding?
He was hanging out
with me yesterday
and he turned to
me and he said
"You're half-
Scottish, right?"
No. There is no way...
It cannot be Ross.
Unbelievable!
Why is your family
Scottish?
Why is your family Ross?
He cannot play
at our wedding.
I mean,
everyone will leave.
I mean, come on,
that is just noise!
It's not even a song!
If you listen
very carefully,
I think...
it's "Celebration"
by Kool and the Gang.
( bagpipes continue )
Well, you're
absolutely right.
They are writing me
out of the show.
I don't know exactly
when it's going to happen
but apparently it's
going to be very soon
and then that's... it.
I'm so sorry.
Look, if it was
up to me
you would never
leave the show.
Yeah, thanks.
No, I mean it.
I can't believe they would
do this to you
and to your fans.
I mean, they're going
to be devastated, heartbroken.
They love you so much.
Oh, you're right.
Thank you.
What's your name again?
Joey.
Joey. Well, thank you.
That is so sweet.
Lo-lo-lo-look,
the only reason
I came up to you before
was because...
well, because I'm really nervous
about-about being you.
You know,
if you could
help me capture the-the essence
of the character, you know?
Help me keep Jessica alive.
Please?
All right, Joey,
I will help you...
not because I-I owe it
to this stupid show
but because...
I owe it to Jessica.
Oh, that's great.
Oh, thank you so much.
You're so welcome.
Now, I've been watching
some tapes. How's this?
( with British accent):
Jessica Lockhart will never
step foot in this place again!
Ever!
Well, but... Jessica doesn't
have an English accent.
I can do an English accent?
That baby's going
on my resume.
( knocking )
Hi, Pheebs.
How are you?
Good.
Uh, Pheeb,
remember when we were
in the coffeehouse,
we decided
that I was going
to keep the cute
guy's cell phone?
Yeah.
And remember how I said
I would keep it in my purse
so that if it rang
I could just pick it up?
Yeah!
Right?
Um, and, then,
do you remember
going into my purse
and stealing the phone?
Ooh, now you lost me.
You stole the phone!
No, I didn't!
No? So you're saying
that if I called it...
it wouldn't ring?
Nope.
Mmm. Okay.
But while you dial,
let me show you the features
of my new ringing handbag.
Mmm.
( phone ringing )
Oh, it does work!
Oh, Phoebe!
That is a different phone.
Oh, is it?
Uh, hello.
Yes, hi, is Rachel there?
Yes, she is. Just
one moment please.
It's for me!
Yeah, that is damning evidence.
( phone ringing )
Oh, my God!
I bet that's him.
My digital fairy tale
is about to begin.
Would you stop doing that?
Hello.
Yes, I'm the one
who found your phone.
Phoebe, you can't...!
I'm on a call.
Oh...
I mean, yeah,
you could pick it up tonight
at, say, 8:30...
at... at my apartment.
It's, um, it's, um,
5 Morton Street, Apartment 14.
And then, maybe,
you know, after
we could grab
a bite to eat or whatever.
Okay, well, okay,
I'll see you then. Bye.
You do know that I will
be here when he comes over.
Oh, and how will you know
what time to come over?
You just said it.
Oh.
The essence
of the character
is rooted in
her confidence.
So, when Jessica enters
a room, for instance
she owns everything
and every person
in that room.
You try it.
Okay.
Right. Well, he's
not mad at the room.
Try it again.
He owns it.
He owns the room.
It is his.
He owns, owns,
owns the room!
He owns it!
All right, it's a
little weird, but
it's getting better.
Oh, I'm going to miss
this woman so much.
I-I don't know what
I'm going to do.
I mean, it's been
20 years of my life.
Oh, then...
Hey, hey!
Maybe... maybe, uh
maybe this is a good
thing, you know?
It'll give you a chance
to shake things up...
play different
characters.
You're so talented.
I probably should've
just left years ago
when the offers
were pouring in
but, you know, I just got
so comfy here and...
Oh, I turned down
some amazing work.
Like what?
Well...
let's just say
if I left 15 years ago
the landscape of Mexican cinema
would be very different today.
Wow.
But... well, now...
now is a different time
for me.
Oh, hey, come on.
Don't... don't do this.
Um... Look, let me tell
you something, okay?
Now, when I watch
you do a scene
I'm thinking, "Boy,
she-she is a great actress"
but... but... I'm also
thinking, "She is hot!"
You think I'm hot?
You own the room.
We should probably
get... get, uh...
Oh, yeah, yeah.
We should get...
So, when Jessica...
kisses a man...
she usually puts, um...
both her hands on the...
man's face.
Yeah, I noticed that.
Is that 'cause she's
so passionate?
No, it's because that way
the camera only sees her.
Oh.
You want to try it?
Yeah. Okay.
That was good.
That was really good...
but I-I think
that maybe your hands are
just a little off.
They should be, maybe,
like, right... right...
( grunting )
Well, I feel like a snack.
Do you want
some shortbread?
It's Scottish,
like you are.
Oh, no, thanks.
I don't like anything
from my Scottish heritage.
What?
Well, it's just
that my entire family
was run out of
Scotland by...
Vikings.
Oh, it sounds to me
like your family is ready
to, uh, rediscover
its Scottish roots.
You can't play bagpipes
at the wedding.
How did you know about that?
We heard you play
all the way from
your apartment.
Were you the ones
who called the cops?
That's not really
important right now.
( clears throat )
What is important is while
we appreciate the gesture
we just don't feel that bagpipes
are appropriate for our wedding.
Why not?
Because we hate them.
Just-Just give me a
chance to perform for you
and then decide
whatever you want...
and I'm not going to
tell you what song I'm
going to play, either
but, uh, let's just say,
when it's over
I'll bet there'll be a
wee bit o' celebration.
Hey! Hey!
( knocking on door)
BOTH:
Who is it?
Hi. It's Tom. I'm here
to pick up the phone.
Well, why do you get
to answer the door?
Well, why shouldn't I?
'Cause it's my apartment.
Well, then I get to give him
the cell phone.
Okay. Good luck explaining
all the calls to China.
Hi.
Wow, how long
were we arguing for?
Um...
( chuckles )
You're not the man who
left the cell phone.
No. That's my assistant.
Is-is he coming?
Uh... no.
Could you... could you,
uh, give us one second?
Sure.
We'll we be
right back, sir.
Well, what do we do?
I don't know.
Can you believe that?
We're waiting for a hot guy
and then an even
hotter one shows up.
I know.
What?
Rachel, listen...
if you let me have him
then I will really
owe you one.
All right.
All right, Phoebe,
I will let you have him
but you owe me--
you owe me big.
So, which one of
you lovely ladies
am I going to take
to dinner, huh?
Oh, that'd be me... sir.
After you.
Okay, thank you.
Okay.
( whispering ):
Nice.
Well, you certainly
owned that room.
Actually, I rent
the whole place
and I... just got what
you meant. Thank you.
( laughing )
Hi.
JOEY:
Hey.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
Oh! Jessica Lockhart!
In my apartment!
I am such a huge fan.
Well, it's nice
to know that you...
Monica! Monica!
That, uh, that's
my roommate Rachel.
Oh, that explains all
the women's underwear.
Sure.
Oh, my God, it's true!
Oh, my God. Can I just ask you
to do me... just one favor?
Certainly.
Would you slap me?
Would you slap me
right here in the face?
I'd love to, but my lawyer
said I can't do that anymore.
All right, here we go.
All right,
just one more thing.
One-one more thing. Um...
You're a stupid bitch.
I really can't slap you.
Oh!
JOEY:
Here you go.
My God, you're great!
Thanks for stopping by.
See you.
I-I am so sorry.
Oh, no-no-no-no.
Being adored-- I'm used to it.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, my God.
What?
They sent me today's script.
They never send me the script.
They don't?
Well, no. I'm just in a coma.
This must mean I have lines.
Oh.
How does it happen?
Ooh. You get thrown
from a horse into
an electric fence.
( gasps )
What?
Jessica hates horses.
Yeah, well,
I'm guessing after this
she's not going to be crazy
about electricity, either.
Oh...
Loosening the saddle
on Mother's horse was
brilliant, Frederick.
And the electric
fence, inspired.
Thank you, sweetheart.
I can't believe
she's really gone.
Look around you--
all of this is ours.
I don't think so.
Who are you?
What's the matter, Dina?
Don't you recognize your own...
mother?
MAN:
Cut. That was great,
everybody. Thank you.
That was so wonderful!
Oh, I think that you're a better
Jessica than I ever was.
Oh, no.
Well, of course not,
but you were very good.
Thanks.
And guess what? Good news--
I got another job.
Great! Hey, all right!
Wha-What is it?
A film in Guadalajara.
The airport?
No, that's La Guardia.
Ah.
This is... Mexico.
Oh. Whoa.
Well, how-how long
will you be gone?
Eight months.
That's a really long time.
Yeah, but you could
come and visit me.
I bet that you could, uh,
own a few places down there.
You know, I'll tell you,
I should probably buy a
place in the city first.
And I just got what
you meant again.
That is a...
I'll tell you
that's a tricky one.
It's a tricky one.
Well...
Good luck.
You, too.
Okay, now,
uh, remember...
I'm still learning.
( bagpipe squeaking
and groaning )
One, two, three, four!
( squeaky notes
over cacophonous groaning )
You know the song--
sing along!
( bagpipe resumes )
( screeching "Celebration"
by Kool & the Gang )
So?
No.